

Curriculum Vitae Jared Govender

Location: Gauteng

Telephone: 060 579 9443

Email: jaredgovender0211@gmail.com

License Code: 10

Professional profile

I have obtained my Bachelor of Science degree in Information Technology and a 3-year diploma in information technology. I am also completing my Front End Development course at Codespace . I am an enthusiastic and adaptable individual who takes pride in my work. I am ever willing to take on new challenges and work towards developing and establishing a better clientele and work environment. My work ethic and studies have taught me to learn through the experiences and knowledge of individuals to excel in the tasks allocated to me in applying dedication and commitment.

Skills:

Front-end development
Back-end development
Creative
Communication skills-writing & Speaking
Extremely hands on
Innovative Self-driven
Trading financial markets
Online marketing

Learning & Development

E-commerce
Information Systems,
Web Technology,
Networks,
Software Development
Networks, Database,
Information Systems,
Operating Systems, C++
Basic Internet Programming
Networks
Java programming
Information technology
Trading the markets

Projects:

Github link: https://github.com/btcon7

- digital-resume
- tic-tac-toe
- memory-app
- percentage-calc
- todo-list
- login-form
- Car detailing website

Education & qualifications:

Codespace -Front End Development
Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (3years) at
Richfield Technology – 2018
Diploma in Information Technology (3years) at Richfield – 2017

Matriculated at Strelitzia Secondary School - 2014
References/Certificates available on request
Currently working on Microsoft certifications (Cloud based)
Codespace Academy

Career Summary:

2021-2021 Mr Price Group Head Office IT Store project Facilitator

- iPad Setups
- MPOS
- Admin
- Stock Control

2019-2020 Lancet laboratory.IT Support Technician IT service desk Key Responsibilities:

- Hornbill Usage
- Resetting passwords
- Emails, MS office 365.
- Pc related problems (software & hardware).
- Printer related problems (Software Related).
- Meditech Related (Lancets database software).
- Admin Related Work (Maintaining and Tracking of all IT equipment, software and hardware).
- Queries Related to software and hardware telephonic aswell as ticket related.
- Upgraded all Pc and laptops to windows10 and removal of Kaspersky and upgrading to Symantec antivirus (Whole KZN region).

Field Technician Key responsibilities:

- Installing and Configuring applications onsite
- Hardware and Software setup/configurations.
- Networking related (cables, patching of servers, setting and running full cables for new labs with all network equipment's.
- Telephones (VOIP, PABX)
- Interface Related problems (Roche, daymed, biofire, labX)
- Printer Installation and issues that can't be solved remotely.
- Repairs, PC and laptop setup -full IT support. Lab setups. (Projects that require fully setup laboratories.)
- Troubleshooting analysers onsite when it does not work remotely (machines that help med techs to analyse samples timelessly.)
- Assisting Pathologists, Dr's, Management and staff with any IT related issues.

2018 Mancosa. Graphic Design Curriculum Development Intern

Key responsibilities:

- Engaging with different IT systems therefore expanding my abilities and knowledge and adapting to different backgrounds and systems, such as:
- Web development (basic) (HTML basic)
- Graphic designer curriculum development, making use of MS Word, PC setup/ installations. Adobe Editing / Adobe suite editing. Team work/assignments.

2017- 2018 Global laboratory

IT Admin and Assistant outline interacting with customers telephonically, General IT maintenance, working with a team, meeting targets.

Key Responsibilities:

- Tasks involved such as Data Capturing, MS office, Global works.
- Xcel spread sheets
- PC setups/installations
- General maintenance with regards to Hardcore/Soft core systems.
- Converging telephones, PC Programs
- MS products, system collections
- Remote Desktop work, Internet installations

2017 8th SA AIDS Conference Key Responsibilities:

- Onsite registration, usher coordinator, sound setup/maintenance.
- Computer systems, obtained working certificate during the time, dealing with customers.
- MS office products, captured data, Key Achievements/Projects